clara.io 2015-03-17

# · Clara.io

Exocortex Technologies Inc. (“Exocortex” or “we”) appreciates your trust and we are committed to being careful and sensible with your personal information. This policy covers the Clara.io website (“Website”) and your interactions with it. However, this policy does not cover your interactions with any external sites that you may visit from links on the Website.

**Personal Information**

Personal Information (“Personal Information”) means recorded information of identifiable individuals provided by the users on Website. Personal Information does not include aggregate information that can not be connected to an identifiable individual.

**Information Gathering and Usage**

During registration we will ask for information such as your name, email address, billing address, and credit card information. Members who sign up for the free account are not required to enter a credit card. We also collect the emails addresses of those that communicate with us via email..

We do not share or sell your information to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, with the exception specified in the section “Legal Disclaimer.”"

We will use the collection information for the following: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research. Additionally, information entered into the optional public aspect of your profile will be displayed on your public Website profile page.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small data file, which includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site‘s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Website requires users accept cookies to gain access. We use cookies to record current session information, but do not use permanent cookies. You will be required to re-login to your Website account after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents.

**Contact**

We will use the contact information you have provided with us in order to send you newsletters regarding product developments and promotions. You are able to opt-out of these newsletters.

We may also contact you directly using your contact information for quality control purposes and for custom support purposes regarding errors or issues on Website Website.

**Children Under 13 and Teens**

This website is not directed at individuals under the age of 13. If a child has provided personal information to the Website Website without consent, please contact us. We do not knowingly collection such information and if discovered, we will terminate the associated account.

**Content**

Exocortex respects your privacy and, unless otherwise required by law, we will not collect, use or disclose your personal information without your prior consent. Your consent may be expressed or implied. You may expressly give your consent in writing, verbally or through any electronic means. In certain circumstances, your consent may be implied by your actions.

**Changes**

Exocortex may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Website primary account holder account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

**Legal Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to share your personal information in order to to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of “Terms of Service”, or as otherwise required by law.

In the event that Website is acquired or undergoes a corporate transaction, Exocortex will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**Questions**

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to [support@exocortex.com](mailto:support@exocortex.com).
